BEASTLY GIRL
I'm shut up in this non-place.
I died because of you.
Yugo!
Maybe you can tell us
what we're supposed to do now.
Everyone has lost it.
I can't get anything out of them except:
"We'll talk about it later",
or "Go ask Yugo."
I don't know, Elely.
I need a little more time.
I've already given you an hour!
My mom and my brother are waiting for us!
I don't believe it! Papa?
I said later, Elely.
Dally, I think you should look up.
Don't you start too, Rubi.
Don't "later" me, you waste of space!
I don't care about the others,
You're not allowed to give up.
Now let's go and save Mama and Flopin...
now!
I don't know what owl-face said,
but it doesn't matter.
You're an Iop
and Iops don't think, they act!
Iops can overcome any challenge.
Are you an Iop or not?
-I'm an Iop!
-Good.
Because while you guys
were all sniffling like princesses...
...I was trying to open the door
to the tower.
And guess what?
We're out of luck. It's jammed shut.
Want to bet?
-Ready, Rubi?
-Always, buddy.
It's pretty solid.
Stop it, Dally.
Can't you see it's no use?
When he's in this state,
nothing can stop him, Amalia.
What an Iopbrain!
At least he's doing something.
Can't we take a little break?
We're not going to force that door open,
Dally. There has to be another way in.
Finally, some common sense.
Yugo's right,
there's some kind of puzzle to solve.
Why else would two big clocks
be on the door?
I don't know how
I didn't notice it before!
This door is made of silver,
very special silver.
-Pure.
-What's got into him?
The plinth is made of palladium,
but it's encrusted with diamond powder.
Fascinating.
Well, it looks like
Ruel's getting into this.
I'll say.
What a delight!
Naturally, gold for the handles.
That's nice, Ruel, but how do we get in?
No keyhole, no need for a key.
There must be a mechanism.
And these can't just be for decoration.
There's a one on the first one
and a two on the second.
Female intuition, coming through.
See? That wasn't so hard. Who's the best?
Amalia!
She's been completely pulverized.
Not quite. Look there!
You owe me again, Amalia.
You're always there when I need you.
Oh, they're in love!
Move aside, lovebirds,
I think I've got it.
Only twice a day, all the ones
and all the twos are lined up.
Morning, at 11:11...
And at 22:22.
Well done, Ruel.
You've made yourself useful for once.
I promise I'll come back and see you
when all this is over.
For now, my darling, my duty calls.
That smell... Ugh!
-It stinks worse than Ruel's feet.
-Well, almost.
I see my usefulness
has been forgotten already.
And I've got an old saying for you, Dally:
"Before you laugh at others,
make sure your own teeth are white."
My teeth are just fine!
Your foot just made a funny noise, Papa.
It's...
It's not the noise I'm worried about.
There! That's...
Count Harebourg. He must have
done something to annoy Oropo.
No! It's...
It's a nightmare!
It's just a little poop!
Poop!
It's everywhere! This place is a pigsty!
Your legend will never survive this, Papa.
Now I won't be the only one here
with stinky feet.
No. No!
No!
Look! I'll follow them.
Wait, Yugo, we can't get separated.
No! This can't happen to a princess!
What are you doing, Papa?
Don't be such a baby.
Everything will be fine!
You... You promise?
I've already lost one foot
in this battle, Elely.
You must be starving.
Please, eat something.
Wait, Flopin.
I don't see any reason to trust you.
I understand that you are wary.
You probably will be for some time.
There is divine blood
in your children's veins, Evangelyne.
They're the first
to have received a proper education.
All other members of our brotherhood
are orphans.
At least this door isn't booby-trapped.
Find anything?
Not really. I just followed
a group of frogs and they opened it.
Wood and stone? This thing has nothing
on that little beauty downstairs.
If we want to find Eva and Flopin,
we need to get
to the top of this tower quickly.
What an outstanding deduction!
That's exactly right.
Don't be strangers, now.
Come on in.
Wait! That was a little girl's voice.
This'll be easy!
Elely, wait!
Good boy, Cancan, good boy.
You did a good job.
My name is Mishell.
I was in such a hurry to meet you,
I sent my Bogart looking for you.
Well, your Bogart is a big slob
and he attacked our feet!
The mighty Percedal, defeated by a poop!
They don't make heroes like they used to.
You know who we are?
Of course I do, Elely.
We're always talking about you guys here,
especially... you!
Me?
Oropo thinks you'll make
an excellent Iop goddess.
That's the only reason
he hasn't beaten you all to a pulp.
He's trying to convince you.
If he wants to convince me of anything,
he'd free my mom and my brother.
You still have plenty of doubts,
like I did.
You'll soon see Oropo isn't our enemy.
On the contrary, he's our savior.
Our savior? That's a bit much.
It's the truth, though!
We don't have time to play around!
I've got a bad feeling about this, guys.
Mishell!
I don't know what you want,
but we want to save our friends.
Every minute we waste increases
the chance that they're in trouble.
Adamai and Oropo
have told us a lot about you, Yugo,
about your great bursts of heroics
that put everyone in danger.
Your friends are fine.
Our leader is not a murderer.
As for what I want from you,
honestly, not much.
Oropo asked me to test you,
so I'm testing you.
If you succeed, you may continue.
If not, you'll stay here
with me and my friends!
Too slow, portal master.
I've never seen anyone react so quickly.
Don't be fooled by appearances.
Like Elely, I'm the daughter of a god,
the god Osamodas!
I don't believe this.
There are demigods in every nook
and cranny of this blasted tower.
Let's get a move on. All we need to do
is get to the other side. I'll create...
I didn't catch that last bit.
Are you okay, Yugo?
Why are you looking at me like that?
There's plenty to go round.
You, too, old man.
Nice work again, Papa!
Congratulations, kid!
You touched our heads!
Unless you want a good spanking,
tell that ugly pet of yours to...
Unless my ears are mistaken,
it sounds like you
are the temple's new Tofus!
Papa!
You turned them into Tofus!
Just for a few minutes.
I wanted time to talk to you.
Follow me, I want to show you something.
They can join us when they change back.
Be good, little Tofus. I'll see you soon.
So, what's the big plan? You're going
to try to convince me you're good guys?
Nope, that's Oropo's job. I'll tell you
my story and you decide what you think.
You mean
we're not going to fight each other?
No.
Not even a little slap?
You'll make a perfect Iop goddess.
Elely, I'll be honest with you.
I hate violence,
especially against animals.
I want to change things.
I want to wake up my friends!
I'm not here to convince you
of anything, Elely.
I think Oropo is right about one thing.
The gods aren't doing their jobs right.
And you want to do it instead?
Do you think you're good enough?
They live like kings,
hiding away in their divine dimensions,
without a care in the world,
especially not for us.
-My dad used to be the Iop god and--
-And he quit, didn't he?
-He didn't even know he was the Iop god.
-Hey, pipsqueak!
-You'll regret treating us like that!
-Stop it, Papa. She means us no harm.
Yeah, you're not the one who almost
got swallowed whole by Big Blue.
It looks like your stay here is over.
Yeah, except it's not you who's
kicking us out! We're leaving.
Elely, don't forget what I told you.
Oropo thought that you could become
a great Iop goddess.
Well, Elely will wait till she's 18
before she becomes a goddess.
I don't know what makes you trust Oropo,
but you should keep your distance.
And you should really join us.
You'll understand soon.
Elely!
Be careful on the next level up.
The tenant gets a little hot-headed.